(Penny:)Oh, damn. They cancelled my Visa.
(Penny:)Oh, yay, a new MasterCard.
(Sheldon:)Uh-oh.
(Penny:)-What?
-I was going to get my mail.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Penny:)Are you hoping to get it telepathically?
(Sheldon:)I think you mean telekinetically.
(Sheldon:)And no.
Wasn't sure of the protocol now you
and Leonard are no longer having coitus.
(Sheldon:)Ugh.
(Penny:)God, can we please just say
"no longer seeing each other"?
(Sheldon:)Well, we could if it were true.
(Sheldon:)You live in the same building.
You see each other all the time.
(Sheldon:)The variable which has changed
is the coitus.
(Penny:)Okay, here's the protocol.
(Penny:)You and I are still friends,
and you stop saying coitus.
(Sheldon:)Good. I'm glad we're still friends.
(Penny:)-Really?
-Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)It was a lot of work
to accommodate you in my life.
(Sheldon:)I'd hate for that effort
to have been in vain.